[
    { "Problem" : "\\sin(30^{\\circ})", "Solution" : "\\frac{1}{2}"}, 
    { "Problem" : "\\cos(30^{\\circ})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\tan(30^{\\circ})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{3}"},
    { "Problem": "\\sin(\\frac{\\pi}{6})", "Solution" : "\\frac{1}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\cos(\\frac{\\pi}{6})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\tan(\\frac{\\pi}{6})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{3}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\sin(0)", "Solution": "0"},
    { "Problem" : "\\cos(0)", "Solution": "1"},
    { "Problem" : "\\tan(0)", "Solution": "0"},
    { "Problem" : "\\sin(\\frac{\\pi}{4})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{2}}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\cos(\\frac{\\pi}{4})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{2}}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\tan(\\frac{\\pi}{4})", "Solution": "1"},
    { "Problem" : "\\sin(45^{\\circ})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{2}}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\cos(45^{\\circ})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{2}}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\tan(45^{\\circ})", "Solution": "1"},
    { "Problem" : "\\sin(60^{\\circ})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\cos(60^{\\circ})", "Solution": "\\frac{1}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\tan(60^{\\circ})", "Solution": "\\sqrt{3}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\sin(\\frac{\\pi}{3})", "Solution": "\\frac{\\sqrt{3}}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\cos(\\frac{\\pi}{3})", "Solution": "\\frac{1}{2}"},
    { "Problem" : "\\tan(\\frac{\\pi}{3})", "Solution": "\\sqrt{3}"}
]